原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     一只虾  Royaa
翻译     小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     房内注意安全罗大  脑子被浆糊住纸袋
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
屏方APP
扫码下载
介个APP成精了
能帮你扒同款☛
104号房间
第一季第十集
都是灰尘
It's dusty.
只有热风
Just hot air.
什么
What?
你还好吗
You okay?
还行  几点了
Yeah. What time is it?
九点四十
Nine forty.
你渴吗
Are you thirsty?
我们刚刚不应该休息的  都怪我  抱歉
We shouldn't have stopped. It's my fault. I'm sorry.
我经常想着  我有一天会去那里的
Like I said, I just always thought I'd go there someday,
所以就可能像...
so it seemed like maybe a...
没关系
It's okay.
我们还有时间
We have time.
你电话设置好了吗
You have the phone ready?
我小时候经常跟我爸去兰堡球场看比赛
My dad and I used to go to games at Lambeau when I was little.
绿湾包装工队是橄榄球联盟里
You know, the Packers are the only
唯一一支由公众共同拥有的球队
community-owned team in the NFL.
1984年的时候  教士队的老板
Well, the owner of the Padres
也想要资助这球队
tried to donate the team
去代表美国圣迭戈市
to the city of San Diego in 1984,
但法律不允许
but the league wouldn't allow it.
系统阻止了
The system prevented it.
电话设置好了没
You have the phone ready?
搞定了  我预留了60秒
Yeah, I gave it 60 seconds before it goes,
在电话之后
you know, after the call arms it.
兄弟  介意我进去吗
Hey, um, mind if I come in?
-进来  -嗯
- Come in? - Yeah.
别  我在忙呢
Yeah, no, I'm working.
或许你可以休息一下
Maybe take a break just for a minute.
我们可没有时间休息
We don't have a minute.
你刚刚才说我们还有时间
You said we have time.
如果我们不休息的话
Not if we take a break.
-我要进来了  -不要啊
- I'm coming in. - No!
-我的天  你小心点  -进来能让我安心点  好吗
- Oh, Jesus, be careful! - Look, it'll relax me, okay?
只是
Just...
出去
Get out.
你知道这有多精细吗
Do you know how delicate this is?
当然知道
Of course.
你想把我们俩都害死吗
You wanna get us both killed?
我会很小心的
Look, I'll be careful.
这里面更热了
It's even hotter in here.
抱歉我没能修好那空调
Sorry I couldn't get the AC going.
所以我们要怎么处理这帐篷
So what do we do with the tent?
等我们完事之后
I mean, when we're done.
-烧了吗  -为什么要烧掉
- Burn it? - Why would we burn it?
有我们的基因  证据
DNA. Evidence.
所以我们才在里面弄  不是吗
That's why we're in here, right?
-可以洗啊  -对
- A tent can be washed. - Right.
可如果他们在我们到达目的地前
What if they check the bag, you know,
要检查这包呢
before we get to the spot?
-坚持我们的说法  -好
- Stick to the story. - Right.
-简单明了  -对
- Short and simple. - Right.
-就两句话  还记得吗  -记得
- Two sentences, remember? - Yes.
会没事的
You'll be fine.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是
I just...
都这时候了  这也不重要了吧
I mean, at this point, what does it matter?
跟我说说那支队伍
Tell me about the Packers.
你去看的第一场比赛
First game you went to.
你不用转移我的注意力
Oh, you don't have to Jedi mind trick me.
我没事
I'm fine.
那时我八岁
I was eight.
我本来都不知道  但历史上
And I didn't realize it then, but historically,
那场确实是关键赛
it was a really significant game.
你听说过兰博之跃[一种庆祝方式]吗
Have you ever heard of the Lambeau Leap?
瑞吉·怀特从对方获得进攻者的漏球
R-Reggie White recovered a fumble from the Raiders
然后横向传给了勒鲁瓦·巴特勒
and he lateraled it to LeRoy Butler
由他带球跑到25码触地得分
who took it in 25 yards for the touchdown.
为了庆祝  他跳进了看台的第一排
And to celebrate, he jumped into the first row of stands
一大群粉丝
and a bunch of the fans,
有老有少
I mean, old men, grown men,
他们跟他拥抱然后拍拍他的背
they just hugged him and patted him on the back.
兰博之跃
The Lambeau Leap.
这大概是他们第一次
Probably the first time
与黑人接触
any of them had ever touched a black man...
也包括我父亲在内
my dad included.
如果他没有赢呢
What if he doesn't win?
我要吐了
I'm gonna throw up.
喝点水吧
Drink some water.
我快弄完了
I'm almost done.
你还好吗
You okay?
我可以把电视打开吗
Mind if I turn on the TV?
你想看就打开吧
If it makes you feel better, go ahead.
...记者正在会议中心...
...our correspondent is live at the convention center...
真的吗
Really?
来了很多人...
There's a big crowd...
不能换个台吗
You can't do better than this?
你换好衣服了吗
You getting dressed?
你先洗个澡吧  一身臭汗
You might wanna shower first. It's like a swamp in here.
今晚史密斯成为代表
Gonna be a wild one
场面一定会非常壮观
down there tonight as Smith works the delegates...
支持者认为今晚能有和他交流的机会
Supporters believe tonight is the chance to talk to his base,
实际上  今晚他将着力
but the truth is tonight should be all about
说服大家他能胜任总统这份职务
convincing people that he can do the job and be presidential.
人们能想象到他在白宫的场景吗
Can people picture him in the White House?
这正是问题所在
That's the question.
他的话能引起拿不定主意的选民的共鸣吗
Will his message resonate with undecided voters?
今晚聚光灯将给他大约一小时的时间
The spotlight will be on him tonight for about an hour
展现自己说服大家
to see if, you know, he can accomplish just that.
也有些好消息  迈克
There's some good points here, Michael.
绝对是这一周的压轴好戏
Definitely a big finale to a long week.
我们有必要知道每一次大会都是
I think it's important to know that each convention
独一无二的
has its own story to tell,
我做不到  对不起
从开幕敲槌到最后的掉球仪式
from the opening gavel to the final balloon drop.
-操  -他们想赋予大会
- Fuck! - They're trying to create the narrative
人的性格
of conventions as people.
而这里的选民
What's happening here is that
投票结果是无法预测的
people are proving to be unpredictable in the polling.
...他生命中最关键的一次演讲
...is one of the most critical speeches of his life.
一名代表说大多数选民
One delegate told me a considerable portion of the electorate
并不看好他有当总统的能力
simply did not see him as presidential.
他得向众人展示
His challenge is to reveal himself
他可以领导整个国家的气魄
as someone who can lead a nation.
他没法满足所有人的要求
He cannot be all things to all people,
但他得说服这几百万选民
but his task will be to convince millions
他能胜任总统这份职务
that he's up for the job.
有人担心会有人
There's been some concern that if someone
想要发言或采取行动
wanted to make a statement or do something,
今天正是行动的好时机
that today might be that day,
所以现场安排了很多警卫人员
so we are seeing a lot of police presence.
这绝对符合他的最大利益
It's definitely in his best interest to.
-同意  不过... -我靠
- I agree, but... - Holy shit!
天呐
Oh, my God.
-抱歉  -搞什么
- I'm so sorry. - What the hell?!
那个服务员让我进来的
The maid let me in.
只有他能修好
He's the only one who can fix it.
我们敲了门
We knocked,
但电视太...
but this TV is so...
他有太多事情...
He's had a lot of things on his...
你可以一会再过来吗
Could you just come back later?
我不是故意吓你的
Um, I didn't mean to alarm you.
我一分钟就能做好
I'll be done in a minute here.
最后一个了  弄好我就走了
It's my last one, and then I can get out of your hair.
直接回家
Go home.
抱歉没有早点来  但今天人手不足
I'm sorry we couldn't come sooner, but we're a man short today.
其实我打算出门了
I'm actually on my way out.
你能给我十分钟收拾行李吗
Could you give me 10 minutes to pack up my stuff?
十分钟吗  我五分钟就弄好了
Uh, 10 minutes? I'll be done in five.
-我赶时间  -好吧
- I'm running late. - Well,
我不影响你  你快收拾吧
don't let me stop you. Do what you gotta do.
现在做这个是不是有点晚了
Isn't it a little late for this?
有点  抱歉
Yeah, it is. Sorry about that.
今天真够疯狂的
It's been a crazy day.
因为这个会议市中心堵死了
Traffic in the city is a mess with this convention in town.
平时的路这会儿有三倍堵
I had to drive through the thick of it three times already.
因纳贝特只剩一条小路可走
Innerbelt's down to one lane
希望路就更不用说了
and you can forget about Prospect.
我以为总算经过了堵的地段
I finally think I got a hold on all these road closures
结果到了这里又遇上了堵塞
and come out here and hit another massive jam.
一帮小孩们吵着抗议
Bunch of rowdy kids protesting,
把街上堵得水泄不通
getting into the street, messing up traffic.
老实跟你说
Look, if I'm being honest with you,
我马上要结束今天十二个小时的工作了
I'm at the tail end of a 12-hour day,
我很想快点回家
I would just love to get home
陪我老婆看完演讲
and see the rest of that speech with my wife.
请快点
Please hurry.
谢谢你
I do appreciate it.
不管怎么样
Anyway,
真不知道你怎么能忍受这种温度的
don't know how you could take this heat a minute longer.
你是进城来开会的吗
You in town for the convention?
我看到你的东西了
I saw your, uh, thingy over there.
是的
Oh, uh, yeah.
我...我是进城来开会的
Yeah, I'm, uh, in town for the convention, yes.
看来你要迟到了
Well, I guess you are running late.
我保证我马上就弄好
I'll have this done in a minute, I promise.
我有原则  不和房客讨论政策
I kind of have a rule not to discuss politics with the customers,
但我想你在电视上应该都看到了
but I figured you got it on the TV, so.
是啊  显而易见的事
Yeah, elephant in the room, so to speak.
是啊  的确很明显
Yeah, he's some kind of elephant, that's for sure.
很难忽视
Tough to ignore.
你是这个意思吗
Is that what you mean?
-是的  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah? Well...
他的人气真的很高  对吧
He really gets the juices flowing, you know?
你不是代表吧
You're not a delegate, are you?
不然的话  你现在肯定在会场
I mean, if you were, you'd be in that arena right now, right?
我只是要去参加会后的酒会
I'm just going to the after party.
真不错
Oh, very nice.
-是什么大人物吗  -不
- Some kind of big shot? - No.
我明白
I hear ya.
朋友的朋友是个大人物  对吧
Friend of a friend of a big shot, am I right?
正如我所说
Yeah, like I said,
我一般不和房客讨论政治
I usually don't talk politics with customers,
但这几天城里的人嘴里说的都是这些
but it's all anybody wants to talk about in this town these days.
政治和体育
Politics and sports.
我们就不能直接投给勒布朗·詹姆斯吗
I mean, can't we just vote for LeBron James?
我不是同性恋  但是
I'm not gay, but, boy,
要是勒布朗说要我嫁给他
I'd have to give it some serious consideration
我会考虑一下
if LeBron asked me to marry him.
我可能的好好考虑
I might have to rethink
我当初在同性恋婚姻提案中的立场了
my whole position on that gay marriage thing.
当然了  我只是在开玩笑的
I'm just kidding, of course.
挺好笑的
That's funny.
这里真是热得像地狱一样
Hot as the devil in here.
是啊
Yeah.
你的小家伙呢
Where's your little one?
小家伙
Little one?
我的孩子小时候
When my boys were young,
就喜欢在客厅搭堡垒
they used to build forts in the living room,
一般都用毯子和被子
usually with blankets and sheets.
不过好像没用过真正的帐篷
Can't say they ever used an actual tent, though.
是啊  不  我们带他去野营后
Yeah, no, um, ever since we took him camping,
他就喜欢上了
he's been obsessed with it.
客厅啊  后院啊  屋顶啊
You know, living room, backyard, roof.
我都习惯了  到处都是
I'm so accustomed to seeing it around,
我自己几乎都没注意
I barely even notice it anymore.
-他几岁  -七岁
- How old is he? - Seven.
真的吗
Really?
你看上去很年轻啊
You seem so young.
结婚早吧
Started early, I guess.
是啊  我的是18岁和22岁
Yeah, well, mine are 18 and 22.
疯狂的小混蛋
Yeah, crazy, little bastards.
当然了  他们已经不小了
Of course, they're not so little anymore,
所以我想他们只是疯狂的混蛋
so I guess they're just crazy bastards now.
柯蒂斯  我的长子  他上大学了
Curtis, my older one, he goes to college.
他读的是个娘娘腔的专业  上帝啊
He's a women's studies major, God help us.
小儿子还在念高中
The younger one, he's still in high school.
他是州篮球队队员
He's a basketball player, all-state.
说实话  他们都是好孩子
Well, truth be told, they're both great kids.
总会让你不禁想
You know, really gets you thinking
他们离开后会怎么样
when they leave the house, I'll tell you that.
不知道他们会变成什么样
Just don't know how they're gonna turn out.
只能尽力防守
Just do your best and let 'em go,
交叉手指
cross your fingers.
你说你的小孩在哪里来着
Where'd you say your boy was?
和我妻子一起在家里
At home with my wife.
对
Right, um,
我知道这看起来很奇怪
I know it looks weird,
但我喜欢出差的时候带上
but I like to bring it with me when I travel.
能缓解对他的四年
It makes me miss him less.
那...那不错
That's-- that's sweet.
-怎么样了  -过几分钟...
- How's it going? - A few more minutes and...
就修好走人
I'll be out of your way.
好
Great.
你要来点吗
You want some?
算了吧
I better not.
不过谢了
Thanks, though.
你觉得他能赢吗
You think he can win?
他都走到了今天
He's made it this far.
是啊
Yeah.
不知道这个国家有没有准备好接受如此真实的领导
I just wonder if this country's ready for someone so real.
但是到了十一月  我会给他投票
But come November, he's got my vote.
真不错
Good to hear.
移民  北美自由贸易协定  中东的这些乱子
Immigration, NAFTA, the whole mess in the Middle East.
你们这些人讲得都是有模有样的
Oh, your guy really tells it like it is.
我们这些人
My guy?
不过我告诉你
I'll tell you what, though.
不管谁赢了  街上都会
Whoever wins, there's gonna be
有一大群气坏了的家伙
an army of pissed off people roaming in the streets.
上帝啊
Fucking Christ!
你能小心点嘛
Careful, would ya?!
对不起
I'm sorry.
不
No, um,
我...我反应过度了
I just-- I overreacted.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事
Ah, it's-- it's okay.
我也有紧张的时候
I'd be on edge, too.
今晚对你来说很重要
It's a big night for you.
我修好后  马上就走
I'll just finish up here and then I'll-- I'll be on my way.
还愿意给我酒吗
That offer still stand?
我也不想那么说  但我有点洁癖
Ah, I hate to be that guy, but I'm kind of a germ freak.
能给我搞个杯子吗
Think you could get me a cup?
好的
Sure.
给
Ah, here you go!
Here you go.
这一天真是漫长
It's been a long day.
真不错
Oh, nice.
味道真不错  谢谢
That is very nice. Thank you.
小波本威士忌
Small batch bourbon.
是我一个朋友在肯塔基制的
A friend of mine distills it in Kentucky
然后100一瓶卖给布鲁克林的嬉皮士
and sells it to hipsters in Brooklyn for $100 a bottle.
一百
A hundred bucks?
看来各有所爱了
Wow, everybody's got an angle, I guess.
不是吗
Don't they?
不好意思
Excuse me.
没事吧
Everything okay in there?
没事  马上就好
Yeah, just, uh, give me a second.
-LG的一次性电话吧  -是的
- An LG burner, am I right? - Yep.
我干过几年手机修理
Yeah, I spent a few years in phone repair.
要给我看看吗
Want me to have a look?
不用
No.
你确定吗
You sure?
好了
There you go.
一切都没事吧
Everything okay?
如果你有一台时光机
If you had a time machine...
你能回到过去
and you could go back in time
阻止希特勒变成希特勒...
and prevent Hitler from becoming Hitler...
你会去的  对吗
you have to do it, right?
时光机
A time machine?
是啊  就像《回到未来》
Yeah, like "Back to the Future."
德洛雷安
A DeLorean.
每小时88.8英里  你就能回到过去
88.8 miles per hour, you can go back in time,
你能回到1930年的德国
specifically, you go back to Germany circa 1930,
你和希特勒在一个城市
you're in the same city as Hitler,
一个房间  你有一把枪
same room, you have a gun.
你会动手吗
Do you do it?
会吧
Yeah.
-我想我会的  -你会吗
- I guess I would. - You would?
是啊
Yeah.
我是说  谋杀的确是没啥
I mean, murder is murder.
的确是一种罪
It'd still be a sin, I suppose,
但那好像是正义的
but that one would seem justifiable.
我想我会有那个勇气
I'd like to think I'd have the guts to do it.
对
Right.
不过要是那个时光机坏了
Get pretty sticky, though,
那可就难办了
if that time machine broke down.
我是说  你杀了希特勒后
I mean, after you killed Hitler.
肯定很难跟在场的那些人解释
It'd be a tough one to explain to the folks in the moment.
"相信我  伙计们  他会做一些坏事"
"Believe me, people, he was gonna do some bad things."
我觉得值得做出牺牲
I think it'd be worth the sacrifice,
想到自己阻止了大屠杀
knowing you prevented the Holocaust.
晚上也能安心入睡
I could sleep at night.
但谁知道会不会有第二个希特勒呢
But who's to say another Hitler wouldn't be waiting in the wings?
另一场大逃杀
You know, a different Holocaust?
只靠一个人是无法杀死两百万犹太人
I mean, one person alone didn't kill two million Jews.
-六百万  -那更加说明我的观点了
- Six million. - Okay, more to my point.
我们算是帮助这个人
So we somehow associate this one man
造成这么多人死亡
with all these millions of deaths...
-是谋杀  -但不是他扣下的扳机
- Murders. - ...but he wasn't the one pulling the triggers.
对吧  不是他扔下的炸弹
Right? He wasn't the one dropping the bombs.
我不知道
Eh, I don't know.
我现在重新考虑  也许我不会动手
I'm rethinking this now. Maybe I wouldn't.
-你不会  -是的
- You wouldn't? - No.
你是说你选择不干掉那个
So you're saying you wouldn't take out the person
策划战争夺走
who devised and implemented the destruction
一千一百万人生命的人
of 11 million human lives?
你刚刚说六百万
You said six million.
六百万犹太人  五百万其他人
Six million Jews, five million others.
如果我知道那样做能阻止这些屠杀
Well, if I knew that it would prevent those deaths,
那当然了  但我要说的是万一不能呢
then, yeah, sure, but what I'm saying is what if it didn't?
但是  嘴上说
And anyway, it's easy to say,
"如果我见到希特勒  我会..."很简单
"If I could've met Hitler, I would've..." Blah, blah, blah,
但没人做到过
but nobody ever did.
所以说明很多人肯定同意他的做法
So that means a whole lot of people must've agreed with him.
你觉得是吗
You think so?
也许他们也恨犹太人
Maybe they hated the Jews, too.
足够杀死六百万人吗
Enough to kill six million of them?
足够接受这件事
Enough to go along with it.
我不知道  他们在那个年代可能就会那样
I don't know, could be they were living in hateful times.
对
Right.
我说了  回头想想
Like I said, it's easy to look back
说自己会更好  是很简单的事
and say you would've been better.
-我们会拒绝  -没错
- That we'd resist. - Yeah.
-我们会做些什么  -是的
- That we'd do something. - Sure.
问题是  我们没有时光机  不是吗
Thing is, we don't have a time machine, do we?
你没看到我的德洛雷安停车在外面吗
You didn't see my DeLorean parked out front?
不好意思
Sorry.
是我妻子  我得接一下
Uh, it's my wife. I have to take this.
我真的快修好了  我马上回来
I really am almost done. I'll-- I'll be right back.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
会议入场证
金色权限
看上不真不错
Whoa, looking sharp!
我该走了  你可以待在这里修好空调
I should really get going, but feel free to stay and finish up.
好吧
All right, well,
等你回来后  这房间会非常凉快清爽
room will be nice and cool for you when you get back.
谢谢
Thanks.
顺便  你可能会见到我儿子
By the way, you might run into my son.
他参与的学校社团
He's part of a school group
这周都在参加会议
that's been at the convention all week,
我妻子刚告诉我
and my wife just told me
他们今晚也受邀参加派对
they got invited to that party tonight.
所以他特别激动
So he's pretty jazzed about it.
他叫杰瑞
His name's Gerry.
不是说你肯定会遇到他  但是谁知道呢
Not that you'll run into him, but who knows?
-杰瑞  -对  我叫史蒂夫
- Gerry. - Yeah. I'm Steve.
和你聊的很愉快
Nice chatting with you.
亚历克斯
Alex.
很高兴见到你  亚历克斯
Good to meet you, Alex.
今晚玩得开心
Have fun tonight,
祝你11月好运
and good luck in November.
谢谢
Thank you.
我要再去一次厕所
I'm actually gonna hit the bathroom one more time.
妈妈
爸爸说你这周五不来了
下周末呢
我再联系你
我爱你
都修好了
All done!
-太好了  -是啊
- Great. - Yeah.
你看看
Check it out.
不了  我该走了
Nah, I-- I should go now.
站在我站的位置  亚历克斯
Stand where I'm standing, Alex.
感受一下
See how it feels.
我要迟到了
I'm late.
你在流汗
You're sweating.
来
Come on.
相信我  你等下会谢我的
Believe me, you'll thank me later.
-我真的应该...  -坐下
- I should really-- - Sit down.
还有那东西吗
Still got that thing in there?
你的杯子
Oh, your cup.
小波本
Small batch, huh?